<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> - Articles</title>
    <description>the craft behind music production.</description>
    <link>
    </link>
    
      
      <item>
        <title>YASPR; A new mid-dark theme for Ableton Live 10</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;By changing a little bit of XML code we can change a lot of the colours that Ableton uses by default. I have always felt that the default themes were a tiny
bit too light or dark. Therefore I decided to create my own theme which is based on Ableton’s Dark theme, except I tried to make it a little easier on the eyes.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>
        /yaspr-ableton-live10-template</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/yaspr-ableton-live10-template</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>:[VIDEO] The history of live looping and how it can be used today!</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;In this article we take a dive in the past and look at how masters such as Terry Riley, Robert Fripp, Brian Eno, etc made use of ‘live loops’ in their performances. What techniques did they use? And are those techniques still relevant today? We’ll also take a look at all the possibilities we have nowadays using modern technology such as Ableton Live 10 and Max 4 Life.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 19:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        /the-history-of-live-looping</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/the-history-of-live-looping</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Do I really need an external preamp?</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Is there any reason to buy different sorts of external preamps? Can’t we just use the build-in preamps that come with our audio interface? Well, yes and no! Let’s find out!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>
        /do-i-really-need-an-external-preamp</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/do-i-really-need-an-external-preamp</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>What are the differences between the different types of compressors? OPTO, FET, VCA, VARI-MU?</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Compression can be accomplished in different ways, hence the different type of compressors. Every different type of compressor sounds different, e.g. one may sound better on certain things than the other. Lets find out how these different types of compressors work, and in which situation we can best use a particular type of compression!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>
        /different-types-of-compression-explained</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/different-types-of-compression-explained</guid>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>
